honorthecode.com 2016-06-16

# PepsiCo Privacy Policy

Effective 2012 (Last updated February 4, 2016)

## This Privacy Policy applies to our sites and apps.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where the policy is located. It also applies to our mobile and social media apps and interactive emails we may send.

This policy does not apply to the websites and practices of other members of the PepsiCo family like Frito-Lay, Gatorade, Quaker, or the PepsiCo Inc. corporate privacy policy. Please visit their websites and read their privacy policies for information on how they use information.

To download a full copy of this Privacy Policy, click [here.] 

## We collect information from and about you.

Contact information. For example, we might collect your name, address, zip code or email address. We might also collect your phone number or other information linked to your identity. 

Information you submit or post. We collect the information you post on our websites or our platforms on third party sites or apps. We also collect information you submit to us.

Demographic information. We may collect information like your gender and age when you sign up on our websites or register for a promotion. 

Other information. If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you're using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it.

Information about third parties. We might allow you to send an email or message to a friend. In that case, we will need that person's name and email address. 

## We collect information in different ways.

We collect information directly from you. For example, if you sign up for our emails or enter a sweepstakes. We also collect information if you make a purchase or fill out an online survey. 

We collect information passively from you. We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We collect information from our mobile apps. We may also collect information about promotion participation or how you interact with our marketing emails. 

We get information about you from third parties. For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you. 

We combine information. For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. Or we may combine information we get from a third party with information we already have. 

## We use information as disclosed and described here.

We use information to respond to your requests or questions. For example, we might use your information to respond to your user feedback. We may use your friend's email address if you use our send-to- a-friend feature.

We use information to improve our products and services. We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We use your information to track and analyze activity on our sites. This helps us improve our sites. 

We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you subscribe with us, we'll enroll you in our email newsletter. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps. 

We use information to customize experiences with our brands. We may analyze information you provide or that we get elsewhere to customize your experience on our platforms and with our brands. To learn more about our targeting and customizing activities, click here.

We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship. We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

## We may share information with third parties.

We will share information within the PepsiCo, Inc. family of brands. This also includes future subsidiaries, affiliates or brands. 

We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or run a promotion. 

We will share information with our business partners. For example, we will share information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion. These partners may send you information about events and products by mail or email. 

We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. 

We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

We may share aggregated information. We may share collective information about our website users with third parties. This information is not personally identifiable. For example, we may tell a business partner how many men or women entered a promotion.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

## You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.

You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails. Visit [http://account.pepsico.com](http://account.pepsico.com/) where you can manage your preferences. You can also opt-out by following the instructions you receive in any of our marketing emails. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you messages about your questions and purchases.

You can control cookies and tracking tools. To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, please click [here](http://policy.pepsico.com/aboutads.htm).

You can control tools on your mobile devices. For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. To modify the push notifications you get from our app, you can alter your preferences in your profile.

We keep a record if you opt out. If you unsubscribe from our database, we keep a record of your information and the unsubscribe action. This is for our internal records. It is evidence of the action and our compliance with this policy.

## We use standard security measures.

We use standard security measures to secure your personal information. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We cannot promise that your use of our site will be completely safe. You use our sites at your own risk.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

## These sites and children.

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. Please note that we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. We reserve the right to limit participation in particular programs or promotions to adults. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can contact us through https://cu.pepsico.com/pepsi. You can also call us at the phone number at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."

Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy online [here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html).

## We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change this Privacy Policy. We will post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates. We will notify you if there is a material to our Policy as required by law. 

## We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don't control.

We include links to third party sites. This may include websites that use the PepsiCo family of brands or logos operated by our advertisers, sponsors, and partners. We do not control those websites. For example, we do not manage the website of The Pepsi Store available at [www.pepsistore.com](http://www.pepsistore.com/). This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. Read the privacy policy of those other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

Our site may also serve third party content that contains its own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies.

## We store information in the United States.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to United States laws. United States laws may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country. If you are located in the European Economic Area and you contact us, information you provide is transferred to the United States.

## Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please call us at 1-800-960-3602.

Or you can email us using our online form: <https://cu.pepsico.com/pepsi>
